[Music]
bright morning everyone Someone asked
What if nothing happens to me can I get
my money back and I want to
get my benefits immediately so are
you one of those questions
when getting an insurance plan if that's
the case this is the perfect plan for
you let me introduce to you sun
accelerate So why accelerate
number eight because this plan only has 8 years to pay
then its maturity
is After 20 years so this product offers
both protection and save
so besides the money you
still have life insurance coverage so let's
talk about What are the benefits
of this plan So this is how the
proposal looks like and this is the
overview of its benefits firstly it is
increasing life insurance coverage
so your coverage increases annually in this
plan secondly at the end of the
20th year when the policy matures the
guaranteed benefit is 102% of the face
amount thirdly it also has a special
bonus and Dividend earnings and
fourthly it also has Increasing
cash benefits If you thought it was over
Well not yet because the client is
entitled to receive annual dividends
starting on the nth year and
he can also take it every year or
he can also leave it with Sunlife to accumulate
and earn interest then what is the Ong paid up
bonus This is will be given after he
pays for 8 years like a graduation
gift like that if he doesn't want to take it
he can leave it with Sun Life to
earn interest again so to
illustrate here's the sample of 30 years
old female non smoker client
he has 1 million fixed amount then
his maturity benefit is
1,000 so after 8 years after he
pays he has received an
endowment
benefit so Increasing cash benefit the
client will receive here so starting 8
years the client will receive is 80,000 and
on the 10th year 100,000 and 100 20,000
on the 12th Year and so on then on the
208th year if you see
only 200,000 listed but
[Music] I will
plug the benefits that the
client got, a total of 80,000 plus maturity
benefit,
PH and a total of 2 million, is that still too much
for what the client paid? So if you want
to learn more about this plan, you know
what to do, send me a message.